const QUIZ =[
    {
        num: 1,
        question: "What is the most haunted room in the Congress Hotel?",
        answers: {
            ans1: "Rm 441",
            ans2: "Rm 666",
            ans3: "Rm 1313",
        },
        correctAns: this.ans3,
    },

    {
        num: 2,
        question: "In 1924 what two rich University of Chicago students  murdered a 14 year old boy \"just because\"?";
        answers: {
            ans1: "Bonnie and Clyde",
            ans2: "Leopold and Leob",
            ans3: "Harry and Carry",
        },
        correctAns: this.ans2,
    },

    {
        num: 3,
        question: "What hotel can a \"Woman in Red\" be seen haunting the 10th floor after supposedly jumping to her death after discovering her philardering husband?";
        answers: {
            ans1: "Congress Hotel",
            ans2: "Hilton",
            ans3: "Drake",
        },
        correctAns: this.ans3,
    },               

    {
        num: 4,
        question: "\"Death Alley\", where 602 dead bodies were placed after burning to death in the new "fire proof" theatre, is located behind which modern-day theatre?";
        answers: {
            ans1: "Globe Theatre",
            ans2: "Nederlander Theatre",
            ans3: "Cadillac Theatre",
        },
        correctAns: this.ans2,
    },

    {
        num: 5,
        question: "Where was John Dillenger, Public Enemy #1, gunned down after being betrayed by a \"woman in red\"?",
        answers: {
            ans1: "Biograph Theatre",
            ans2: "Cadillac Theatre",
            ans3: "Nederlander Theatre",
        },
        correctAns: this.ans1,
    },

    {
        num: 6,
        question: "Roses are red, so is blood. What is was the bloodiest day in Chicago mob histroy?";
        answers: {
            ans1: "St. Valentine\s Day",
            ans2: "Halloween" ,
            ans3: "St. Patrick\'s Day",
        },
        correctAns: this.ans1,

    },

    {
        num: 7,
        question: "Urban legend has that this house, turned museum, was once where a baby, born with scales, horns, and hooves, was abadoned and locked in the attic until its death?";
        answers: {
            ans1: "Driehaus House",
            ans2: "1502 N. Clark St",
            ans3: "Hull House",
        },
        correctAns: this.ans3,
    },

    {
        num: 8,
        question:"In what neighborhood was H.H. Holmes' murder castle located?",
        answers: {
            ans1: "Lincoln Park",
            ans2: "Pilsen",
            ans3: "Englewood",
        },
        correctAns: this.ans3,
    },

    {
        num: 9,
        question: "Both Jeffery Dahmer and John Wayne Gacy have been said to frequent this Lakeview tavern";
        answers: {
            ans1: "Richard\s bar",
            ans2: "L&L Tavern",
            ans3: "Green Mill Cocktail Lounge",
        },
        correctAns: this.ans2,
    },

    {
        num: 10,
        question:"This uptown lounge was Al Capone's favorite spot and has hidden tunnels and the occasional ghostly activty.";
        answers: {
            ans1: "Richard\s bar",
            ans2: "L&L Tavern",
            ans3: "Green Mill Cocktail Lounge",
        },
        correctAns: this.ans1,
    }    
]